



Cagil Benibol

Date of birth: 12/02/1998 | **Nationality:** Turkish | **Phone number:**

(+49) 15753284005 (Mobile) | Email address: cagil.benibol@gmail.com | Website:

cagilbenibol.com | Github: https://github.com/Tihulu |

Address: Max Liebermann Str 8, Stw/app 1, 80937, München/Germany, 80937,

München, Germany (Home)

ABOUT ME

A curious Physicist doing his M.Sc. in Germany's leading universities and graduated from Turkey's one of the most outstanding universities with an honors degree. Have strong theoretical background and problem-solving skills. Knows statistical methods and data analysis in Astrophysics and Theoretical Physics. Knows Quantum Computing methods and algorithms. An effective team worker. Experienced in organizing many conferences and science festivals. A professional musician. Plays keyboard and piano in several bands.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 Ankara, Türkiye

QUANTUM COMPUTING QBRONZE AND QSILVER / METU

QTurkey / Practical Quantum Computing for Scientists course was given in METU fall 2022 Final project/ RSA Decryption Algorithm with Shor's Algorithm

2022 - CURRENT Izmir, Türkiye

BACKEND PROGRAMMER FREELANCE

Basically, HTML generating Python Script From Excel Menu to HTML Website generator program. tihulu.github.io/arafta

Link tihulu.github.io/arafta

2020 - CURRENT

KEYBOARDIST MEDITERRA

2-Song Ep "Beni Anlat" and a single "Unknown" MEDITERRA / SPOTIFY, APPLE MUSIC, YOUTUBE and more

2021 - CURRENT

MUSICIAN SOLO PROJECT

Ka-Fa 1500:

8-Song Album "Everyone is Confused" and a 4-Song Ep "The_Trrektor.exe"
SPOTIFY, APPLE MUSIC, YOUTUBE and more

2021 - CURRENT Izmir, Türkive

WEB AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER ARAFTA

QR Code Menu Website Design and Designing of the QR Code Plate on Al and PS.

Link tihulu.github.io/arafta

2021 Izmir, Türkiye

WEB DESIGNER FREELANCER

Portfolio website for Unseverdesign

Link tihulu.github.io/unseverdesign

2019 Eskişehir, Türkiye

ASTRONOMY GUIDE TUBITAK

Sivrihisar Science Fest Organized by TUBITAK (4007 Project)

2018 Ankara, Türkiye

ASTRONOMY GUIDE TUBITAK

Altindag Science Fest Organized by TUBITAK (4007 Project)

2018 Istanbul, Türkiye

ORGANIZATION OF A PHYSICS SUMMIT INTERSCHOLASTIC PHYSICS STUDENTS' SUMMIT (IPSS)

Organization Committee in1st Interscholastic Physics Students' Summit (IPSS) ISTANBUL TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

2017 Ankara, Türkiye

ORGANIZATION OF AN ASTRONOMY CONFERENCE AMATEUR ASTRONOMY SOCIETY OF METU

Organization Committee in 1st Dilhan Eryurt Astronomy Day

2017 ANKARA, Türkiye

MTA MUSEUM GUIDE & PHOTOGRAPHER BIOGEN SOCIETY OF METU

11th Aykut Kence Evolution Conference

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2022 - CURRENT München, Germany

M.SC. QUANTUM SCIENCE & TECHNOLOGY Technical University of Munich & Ludwig Maximilian University of Munich

Website tum.de

2016 – 08/2022 Ankara, Türkiye

B.SC. PHYSICS, HONORS DEGREE Middle East Technical University

Website metu.edu.tr | Field of study Physics | Final grade CGPA: 3.00 /4.00 - Honors Degree with 317 ECTS |

Thesis Estimating Hamiltonian in a Schwarzschild (Black Hole) Metric with Quantum Computers Using VQE Algorithm

2019 – 2019 Istanbul, Türkiye

FEZA GURSEY INSTITUTE HAKKI OGELMAN SUMMER SCHOOL ON "ASTROPHYSICAL MODELING" Feza Gursey Institute, Bogazici University

Website http://fezagursey.boun.edu.tr/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **TURKISH**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1
GERMAN	A2	A2	A2	A2	A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Web: HTML, CSS | Music Production: Logic Pro X, Cubase, Reaper | Others: Photoshop & GIMP, Familiar with Linux & Mac OS environments, Rasp-berry Pi & Arduino | Quantum Computing: Qiskit, Qiskit Aqua, QutiP, Cirq | Computer Languages: Python, C Anaconda Spyder/Jupyter, Spyder MATLAB & Octave | Astrophysics: SAO Image DS9, Fermitools, fermipy, CIAO, CALDB, XSPEC | COMSOL | Microsoft Office package: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

PROJECTS

2022

Estimating Hamiltonian in a 3+0 Schwarzchild (Black Hole) Metric with Quantum Computers Using VQE Algorithm What I tried to understand in my graduation project is the free electron's behavior in a 3+0 Schwarzchild Black hole by looking at its Hamiltonian by using Variational Quantum Eigensolvers.

Link https://github.com/Tihulu/400-Project-Cagil-Benibol

2022

RSA Decryption Algorithm with Shor's Algorithm Final project of a given course, called "Practical Quantum Computing for Scientists" in METU fall 2022

An algorithm that decrypts RSA with Shor's Algorithm on python Qiskit.

Link https://github.com/Tihulu/quantumcomputing/tree/main/project

2020

Gamma & X-ray observations of RCW-86 with Fermi - LAT and Chandra Final project of a given M.Sc. course in METU called "Data Analysis on Astrophysics" in spring 2020.

Link https://github.com/Tihulu/Astr-518

REFERENCES

2022 - CURRENT

References from my undergraduate university

For Quantum Computing: Dr. OSMAN BARIŞ MALCIOĞLU, <u>mbaris@metu.edu.tr</u> For Computational Physics: Prof.Dr. ALİ MURAT GÜLER, <u>amg@metu.edu.tr</u> For Quantum Information: Prof.Dr. SADİ TURGUT, <u>sturgut@metu.edu.tr</u>